Office of the Vice Provost Records UA166
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2017 accessions, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA166.003; 46.8 Linear Feet
  - May 2017 accession, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.001; 13.2 Linear Feet 11 record cartons
    - N/A, N/A: N/A, Misc. Agreements, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 30)
    - Papas, Athena: Massachusetts DPH, Dental Nutrition Manual, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 31)
    - Sollod, Albert: Development Alternatives, Inc., Fixed Price Agreement, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 32)
    - Sokol, Samuel: Research to Prevent Blindness, Inc., RPB Senior Scientific Investigator Award, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 33)
    - Misc.,: Misc., Misc., 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 34)
    - Garibaldi, Barbara: N/A, Personel Event Forms, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 35)
    - Furie, Bruce: New England Medical Center, Human Hybridomas in the Analysis of Autoimmune Disease, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 36)
    - Gregory, Robert: USDA, N/A, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 37)
    - Kessler, Marco: American Cancer Society, ACS Fellowship, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 38)
  - August 2017 accession, ORA Award files, circa 1986 -- 2014; UA166.003.002; 21 Linear Feet
    Transferred by Jonathan Chau, Office of the Vice Provost, 2017, accession UA-2018-029.
    This sub-series is arranged in received order; received order is largely by fiscal year.
    This sub-series contains ORA Grant and Award files from FY12-FY14.
    - 003132-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - 002331-00001, 2010-- 2011; UA166.003.180.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - 003087-00001, 2010-- 2011; UA166.003.180.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - 003021-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - 002607-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - 001928-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - 003325-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - 002915-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - 003684-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - 002293-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - 001698-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.180.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - 003201-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - 001248-00001, 1990 -- 2011; UA166.003.180.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - 002233-00001, 1992 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - 002441-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.180.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - 001679-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - 003054-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - 002464-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - 003716-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - 003534-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - 002006-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - 001086-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 22)
    - 002872-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.180.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 180, Folder 23)
    - 003088-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - 001840-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - 000996-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - 002167-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - 002119-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - 002259-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - 000729-00001, 2001 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - 003633-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - 003821-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - 003225-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - 003213-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - 001693-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - 001687-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - 001856-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - 001772-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - 001864-00001, 2006 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - 002390-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.181.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - 002075-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.181.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - 003328-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - 002634-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - 002407-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - 002639-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - 002926-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - 002423-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - 003111-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - 001779-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - 000997-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - 002693-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - 002063-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - 001664-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - 003000-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - 001147-00001, 2006 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - 003396-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - 003373-00001, 2003 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - 003256-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - 001724-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - 003394-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - 003017-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - 002606-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - 001965-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - 002007-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - 002318-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - 002975-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.182.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - 002290-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - 001006-00001, 2006 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - 002686-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 28)
    - 002251-00001, 2007 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 29)
    - 000592-00001, 1986 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 30)
    - 001926-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 31)
    - 002026-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 32)
    - 001633-00001, 2007 -- 2011; UA166.003.182.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 182, Folder 33)
    - 002278-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.183.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - 001871-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - 001979-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - 002409-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - 001785-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.183.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - 002408-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - 001699-00001, 2007 -- 2011; UA166.003.183.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - 002923-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - 002418-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.183.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - 000958-00001, 1989 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - 003292-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - 003255-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - 003134-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - 001753-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - 000952-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.183.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - 002429-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - 000475-00001, 1996 -- 2012; UA166.003.183.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - 000638-00001, 2001 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - 002422-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - 002332-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - 002149-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - 002151-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - 001980-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - 001103-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - 001964-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - 002365-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - 002319-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - 000393-00001, 2003 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - 002193-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - 002116-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.184.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - 002729-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - 002665-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - 002987-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - 001630-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 17)
    - 003247-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - 002888-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 19)
    - 000918-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 20)
    - 001988-00001, 1987 -- 2012; UA166.003.184.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 184, Folder 21)
    - 001889-00001, 1998 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - 003257-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - 003200-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - 002051-00001, 2009 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - 003221-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - 002317-00001, 2010 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - 002479-00001, 2011 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - 003624-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - 002474-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - 001981-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - 002541-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - 003208-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - 001987-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - 000784-00001, 2006 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - 003875-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - 003243-00001, 2007 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - 001665-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - 001644-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 18)
    - 001294-00001, 2005 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 19)
    - 001767-00001, 2008 -- 2011; UA166.003.185.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 20)
    - 001667-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 21)
    - 003041-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 22)
    - 003228-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 23)
    - 003063-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 24)
    - 003800-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 25)
    - 003798-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 26)
    - 003178-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 27)
    - 002728-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 28)
    - 002816-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 29)
    - 002384-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 30)
    - 002310-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 31)
    - 003443-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 32)
    - 003517-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.185.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 33)
    - 003408-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 34)
    - 003350-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.185.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 185, Folder 35)
    - 001703-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - 002417-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - 002847-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - 002315-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - 003444-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - 003244-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - 002081-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - 002168-00001, 2007 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - 002316-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - 002666-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - 002383-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - 002160-00001, 2000 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - 002413-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - 002178-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - 001152-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - 002712-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - 001046-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - 002765-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - 003020-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 19)
    - 002723-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 20)
    - 002465-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 21)
    - 002638-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 22)
    - 002314-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 23)
    - 002155-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 24)
    - 002330-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 25)
    - 002415-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 26)
    - 003604-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 27)
    - 002967-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 28)
    - 001154-00001, 2007 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 29)
    - 002838-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 30)
    - 002798-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 31)
    - 003334-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 32)
    - 003123-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 33)
    - 002489-00001, 2013 -- 2013; UA166.003.186.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 34)
    - 002881-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.186.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 186, Folder 35)
    - 002428-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - 002973-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - 003046-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - 002928-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - 002823-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - 002873-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - 003024-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - 001860-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - 001710-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - 001183-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - 002476-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - 001771-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - 001080-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - 003252-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - 001798-00001, 2005 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 15)
    - 002207-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 16)
    - 001677-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - 001004-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - 001027-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 19)
    - 003045-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 20)
    - 002574-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 21)
    - 001962-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 22)
    - 002113-00001, 1997 -- 2013; UA166.003.187.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 23)
    - 003419-00001, 2002 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 24)
    - 002802-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.187.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 187, Folder 25)
    - 003419-00001, 2002 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - 001106-00001, 2004 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - 003271-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - 001922-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - 003131-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - 002605-00001, 2010 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - 002281-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - 003115-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - 002858-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - 002003-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - 002539-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - 003136-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 12)
    - 003031-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - 002800-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 14)
    - 002804-00001, 2012 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 15)
    - 002614-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 16)
    - 003130-00001, 2011-- 2012; UA166.003.188.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 17)
    - 003025-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 18)
    - 002903-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 19)
    - 001915-00001, 2005 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 20)
    - 002850-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 21)
    - 000891-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 22)
    - 002781-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 23)
    - 003581-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 24)
    - 002188-00001, 2002 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 25)
    - 002914-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 26)
    - 002291-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 27)
    - 002475-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 28)
    - 001715-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 29)
    - 003044-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 30)
    - 003204-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 31)
    - 001793-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 32)
    - 003386-00001, 2011 -- 2012; UA166.003.188.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 33)
    - 001154-00001, 2007 -- 2013; UA166.003.188.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 188, Folder 34)
    - 001995-00001, 2003 -- 2012; UA166.003.189.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - 001865-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.189.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - 001813-00001, 2009 -- 2013; UA166.003.189.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - 002938-00001, 2012 -- 2013; UA166.003.189.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - 001801-00001, 2008 -- 2012; UA166.003.189.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - 002994-00001, 2011 -- 2013; UA166.003.189.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - 003199-00001, 2009 -- 2012; UA166.003.189.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - 003277-00001, 2010 -- 2012; UA166.003.189.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - 003268-00001, 2008 -- 2013; UA166.003.189.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - 000497-00001, 1997 -- 2013; UA166.003.189.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - 000497-00001, 1997 -- 2013; UA166.003.190.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - 002065-00001, 2007 -- 2012; UA166.003.190.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 190, Folder 2)